Shubham Rishi

Abbotsford, BC V2S 5N8 shubhamangras@hotmail.com +1 236 458 1757

I love learning, as it is a lifelong process. Currently, I am a full-time student who is pursuing his bachelor's program in the field of computer science from UFV.I have a lot of experience related to Computers(Software and Hardware). I would love to gain valuable experience which will be beneficial for me in the future.

I have:

- Over 2 years of experience in Web Development, Programming, operating systems, and troubleshooting through education and work experience
- · Coding practice includes thorough code reviews, careful debugging and other techniques
- Detail oriented and accurate with strong numerical and mathematical knowledge of methods and skills for computer aided design
- Effective team player with demonstrated interpersonal and communication skills
- Dependable, hardworking, efficient, and quick learner
- Fluent in English, Punjabi and Hindi

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Computer Lab Monitor

University of the Fraser Valley - Abbotsford, BC January 2022 to Present

- Monitored Library Computer Lab with Printing Facility.
- Monitored Library Computer Lab with Printing Facility.
- · Responsible for troubleshooting computer hardware, printer and network related issues

Web Developer, IT Technician

Terranotics Tech Solutions Inc. - Abbotsford, BC September 2020 to Present

- Perform Business to Business Interaction with Potential Clients and Discuss with them on how technology will give a positive impact to their Business.
- Design, maintain and Host Static and Dynamic Websites using various programming languages.
- Provide Technical Support to Customers. (Hardware and Software)
- Maintain Google Business Listings, Perform SEO and Generate ads.

Produce Clerk (Part-time)

Chalo Freshco - Abbotsford, BC June 2021 to January 2022

- Maintained friendly and professional customer interactions
- perform the quality control of the products by regular based calling of the individual items.
- · Moved seasonal product to high flow areas to increase impulse purchasing and sales
- Organized inventory and performed breakdowns of produce

• Interacted with customers and worked closely with produce team

Merchandiser

Shoppers Drug Mart / Pharmaprix - Abbotsford, BC March 2019 to September 2020

- Actively attended to customers and provided appropriate recommendations based on customer needs
- Conducted inventory management and data entry with high accuracy
- work closely with the executive team in strategizing long and short-term goals
- Assisted customers in locating items as well as performing duties as a cashier

Store Associate

Big Box Outlet Store - Abbotsford, BC May 2018 to November 2019

- Market products with a value approach
- Educate customers on the features and benefits of the products.
- Demonstrated personal selling and value-based selling skills
- Manage inbound customer inquiries and provide solution-based recommendations to ensure customer satisfaction

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer science

University of the Fraser Valley - Abbotsford, BC May 2018 to Present

Skills

- JavaScript
- CSS
- PHP
- Java
- MySQL
- Git
- HTML5
- XML
- Linux
- C/C++
- User Interface (UI)

Languages

- English Expert
- Hindi Expert
- Punjabi Fluent

· Sanskrit - Expert

Links

https://angrasys.github.io/

Certifications and Licenses

Introductory digital marketing

March 2020 to Present

It was an online certification by google about digital marketing

Additional Information

SKILLS

- Reliable team worker
- Neat, clean and professional appearance
- Excellent multi-tasker
- punctual
- Customer service oriented
- Time management

SHUBHAM RISHI

1-2830, BOURQUIN CR.WEST ABBOTSFORD, BC, CANADA, V2S5N8